Oh, hey! Good morning!
Oh, she's wearing her summer uniform.
Hey, you on Yakisoba?
Okay, but I didn't ask.
Crap, we changed uniforms as of today.
Maybe I can just casually dress down.
Feels like summer's here already now that we changed out our uniforms.
Even though we only swap out our cardigans for vests?
These skirts are completely different, too.
Feel for yourself.
Why are you openly half-undressed like that?
Um, beats me.
Summer already. I hate this time of year, but this time around, kid, you have Yamada.
Get lost. Don't go letting wicked hopes like that build up.
Not like anything even happened over Golden Week. She's been super busy lately, too.
You sure seem in a good mood.
Let me guess, you got the part from that audition?
That info's not public knowledge!
What's this about?
Huh? Nothing, just...
Good morning, class!
Today's a big day, so let's pick our groups for the school trip.
I hope we're together.
Yeah, me too.
Gotta split into groups, huh?
The 12th...
Something the matter?
What? No, it's nothing.
What?
Oh!
Uh, coming!
Ichikawa!
Huh?
Let's group up for the trip.
We can ask Yamada, too.
What?
Yamada?
But why?
What do you mean, why?
Aren't you friends?
Mm-mm...
Come on!
Put it up!
Don't give me it!
I'll go ask, then.
Huh?
Come on, then!
That's annoying!
Let me squish that sandwich!
Hm?
What's the matter?
If you still need someone, I don't mind joining up with you.
Huh?
Hey, girls!
Ichikawa says he'll join!
Hm?
Sorry, we're only picking roommates here.
What?!
But...
But Kanzuki said...
I was talking about Tepe Yamada.
Obviously.
Huh?
Why does nothing ever go right?
Oh...
Huh?
Uh...
Hm.
What's going on?
She doesn't seem like herself.
It's like something's bothering her.
A first kiss?
Ah!
Ugh!
The school trip arc of Kimi-Iro Octave has a first kiss scene.
There's a real chance this is on her mind.
Get out of here!
Ugh.
Is she thinking about that?
On our trip?
They're completely soaked.
Yeah.
Uh...
Here.
Huh?
Uh...
I can do this myself, thanks.
But I want to.
No way!
Uh...
What am I thinking?
Get in crap!
School trips are a waste of time!
What's fun about being stuck in a room with people I'm not even real friends with?
Uh...
are a waste of time what's fun about being stuck in a room with people I'm
not even real friends with this is weird why did I hang on to this even though I
didn't go hmm am I actually looking forward to this
oh you're still up oh is that volume 12 there oh sure is bought another copy so
you can keep that one I lent you Yamada's rereading it to volume 12 the
one with the kiss scene during their school trip so I am I wanted to talk
about our upcoming school trip oh okay
well so I wanted to discuss something on your mind huh well see
actually never mind huh I'm gonna go I will so be there so what was this about
hey can I turn off my video
so uh no any good food they might have in Nora no maybe some deer crackers let's
stick to people food and just like that with no real rhyme or reason I was left
feeling uneasy and somewhat concerned hey you sick
soon enough we were off on our trip to Nara and Kyoto
miss Moria what's wrong Anna already ate all the snacks she brought for the school trip
before we boarded is it okay if I go stuck up on snacks again and pretend you didn't eat all
the snacks you were allowed yeah I don't think so
your bag sure is full
I thought it'd make a good tag you think so for what for my bag here's a thought sit down okay
moiko let's trade that window seat every five minutes I don't think so
sheesh how'd this happen
wanna switch seats would you
oh
high-rise apartments in the middle of rice fields how strange what's demand like for
those huh okay then
Ichikawa yeah you should probably be careful next three days
why careful about what exactly see Kana there
she's making celebratory confetti she wants to pair some couple up during this trip
she made us all practice our flash mob act too
you should know you and Yamada are her top targets right now
what but um me and Yamada are you know
then maybe I don't need to warn you
you honestly want to be forced by your classmates to ask her out
are you the sort that needs to be pushed into it
I'm I'm fine I can do it myself now
you don't mind if I recline back do you I do mind
why sit down make me what are you three hurry up and turn around
love is strange
I need to be careful best way to avoid causing a scene is to keep my distance from Yamada
as long as we're not together they can't celebrate for us
but just my luck we're stuck in the same group
aren't you all gonna give them some delicious crackers
be careful
why
love what
hey wait
sis too
stop
sis
hey I'm just kidding you want you trying to gather all the gear and I know
what
hey
incoming
huh
wait
yo
hang on
don't move
right where you are
now back up
what are you doing to me
what
I need to get away
what are you doing
excuse me Yamada
wait stop
where are you going
this ought to be far enough away
huh
you lost
what
she's being weird
isn't she
what
you haven't noticed
you're right
she's definitely faking that enthusiasm
she's made this choice all on her own
so there's not really much I can do about it now
but it just doesn't sit right with me
a choice
yeah
sounds like she knows something
finally
this is where you've been
what kind of group leader runs off alone
sorry
let's get going
bye
later
she made this choice herself
what choice
can't believe you're really eating it
huh
where'd you go
the bathroom
how do they taste
we shouldn't be alone together
we can't be
but still
okay everyone ready
Nara's deer are real
cute
I want to know
how she feels
the first night of our trip was here
you're not gonna eat that
yes I am
she seems in a good enough mood
lay off my food
I'm not doing anything
don't steal my precious nutrients
she was like this before though
despite it all
she's really mature and serious about everything
there's got to be something
what
okay
now to just pop in
wash up
and get out
hey
Ichikawa
join us for some dick battles
come on
do it
why are you here
wasn't class 2 in here already
yeah
but
I accidentally walked into the girl's bath
and got yelled at
so
you know
accidentally
think about it though
right about now
the girls are like
oh your boobs are the bigger now
let me get a squeeze
and then they start fondling each other see
so
we ought to
have a dick battle
for the sake of gender equality and all
wow Adachi
you're really growing up
whoa
Kanzuki
no way my man
that's crazy
what can I say
wait
Ichikawa
no way
why me
did you kill
nothing beats a nice luxurious bath
huh
what's the matter with all of you
it doesn't feel all that right to me
seeing for free
I know how you feel
well I'm gonna take this chance
that'll be a thousand yen per second
one thousand
two thousand
three thousand
that hardly seems very
four thousand
been in long enough already
gonna head out
me too
what
think it's okay to swim around
no
aww
you enjoying the trip
so far I mean
yeah
I like it a lot
time to get back
and stake my claim
on the blow dryer
okay go ahead
I'll catch up with you later
cool
see ya
huh
what
Yamada
that was close
thanks
uh-huh
Kimi-Iro Octave AD
thank goodness
here they are
time to get the coins
from the back too
uh yeah
hey there
itikawa
there was some epic dick battle
back there huh
dude
you put up a righteous fight
seriously
huh
dang
almost had him
you just saved the day
huh
hmm
day after tomorrow
Kimi-Iro Octave
AD
is that a release date
the last volume just came out though
what is it then
it's obvious
huh
it means the two of you are gonna lock lips on the final day of the trip dummy
just like they did in volume 12
you can't just show up in a place like this
ha
huh
dude what the
uh
harvest room is right under ours
right down there is where she's sleeping
well well
what the
yes yes
perfect
very good
uh
essentially
it'll go like this
what are you doing
oops
don't you worry
uh
focus on how to make the kiss happen
hmm
it's two days away
you're wrong
that's not what's troubling her right now
Yamada
is more serious than that
this is more important
what then
i mean
me too
huh
i'm just saying
i feel the same way
more than anyone in the world
hmm
i need to come out and say it
so listen
i'm not gonna
shy away now
huh
Yamada
i like you
i really do
nigurikawa
i'm enjoying myself
i am
that was
from kimi
you're a octave
she's made this choice all on her own
so there's not really much i can do about it now
oh
sure is
bought another copy
let me guess
you got the part from that audition
an audition
for kimi
so what if it is really that
she wouldn't be on this trip if she thought she'd get it
no you're wrong
a trip like this is a once in a lifetime event
she'll have plenty of other auditions to do
you're wrong
she wouldn't be down there like that if she felt that way
no i mean
that's not the way she thinks about things in the first place
she wouldn't be here just because she didn't have a chance
fine then tell me why is she here
never mind
huh
i'm gonna go
i will so be there
there
for me
that's why
hey
you sick
no
i'm fine
i am
so
very stupid
it's so obvious once i stop and think for a second
yet here i was thinking about a kiss
huh
it's almost lights out
i'll be right back
i of all people know just how seriously she takes the work she does
and this is for her favorite series
she's got to have been practicing like never before going to school to work and practicing with what little time is left but despite all that
because she knew i was looking forward to this even lied my way out of some school events this is my fault
it's my fault
yamada what are you doing that's not your room sorry
yamada
what are you hiding for
well i just
i just
what now
is there someone else over there with you
no
that you kobayashi
what
oh yeah she forgot which room she was staying in
you're both in that room over there
now get inside
there
in you go
goodnight
i'm gonna use these here to do a thing
uh
am i
really
try it too
phew
these group leader meetings are a pain
hey you okay
yeah i just tripped
well be more careful then
uh
wait
what